Next on the list is a very good friend of mine, I'd like to call up Director Blaine
Griffin, who's going to conduct El Hajabir Khalid Samad.
[applause]
City Clerk Director Blaine Griffin joined the Jackson administration in March
2006 as Executive Director of the Community Relations Board.
He leads the staff in an appointed board in improving cross-cultural
relationships throughout the city of Cleveland.
He has efforts to improve intergroup relations and to correct actions of
violating civil rights of individuals.
The Community Relations Board also oversees police and community relations and
youth initiatives in the city.
Prior to working for the city, Blaine worked with the Cuyahoga Department of
Justice Affairs and served as the Program Director for the Hummer Network of
Creative Cleveland.
He's also affiliated with a number of community and professional organizations,
such as serving as President of the Baukeye Shaker and Woodlandville's
Neighborhood Assembly.
Blaine, Director Blaine Griffin.
[applause]